One pilot's heroic mission to hell and back.
Spitfire Over Berlin is a war, action, history film directed by Callum Burn.
August 1944.
With the American Eighth Air Force poised to strike over Nazi Germany, British
Intelligence learns that they could be flying into a deadly trap.
With only hours to spare, Flight Lieutenant Edward Barnes must fly a life and death mission over Berlin
in his unarmed Spitfire to obtain photographic evidence and save the lives of 1200 men.
Edward Barnes, played by Kris Saddler.
David, played by Tom Gordon.
Group Captain, played by David Dobson.
Stanley, played by Vin Hawke.
Spitfire Over Berlin is a 2022 British war film, focusing on
an aerial spying mission during World War II.
Like Burn's prior film, Lancaster Skies, it is a homage to the British war
films of the 1940s and 1950s, and is inspired by true events.